Contact

rfferreira69@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/raquelferreira-msn-rnc-nic-4745b6117 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Registered Nurses NICU

Certifications

Advanced EFM
Certified High Risk Neonatal RN
NRP Instructor

Raquel Ferreira MSN,RNC-NIC

Director of Women's and Children's Services Spring Hill

Summary

Experienced Director of Women's Services with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Electronic Medical Record (EMR), Nursing, Clinical Research, Critical Care, and Neonatal Intensive Care Unit (NICU). Strong operations professional with a Master's Degree focused in Nursing Administration from Norwich University.

Experience

HCA Oak Hill Hospital
Director of Women's and Children, NICU Services
August 2016 - Present (4 years 1 month)

Bayfront Health System
NICU Nurse Manager
October 2015 - July 2016 (10 months)
Bayfront Health SpringHill

24 hour support, management and supervision of a level II NICU

Bayfront Health SpringHill
NICU RN Charge/Clinical Coordinator
October 2001 - October 2015 (14 years 1 month)

Hca Oak Hill Hospital Labor and Delivery/Post Partum/Nursery RN June 1997 - October 2001 (4 years 5 months) LDRP and Nursery RN

Columbus Medical Center NICU RN June 1993 - February 1997 (3 years 9 months) Columbus, Georgia

Level III Nicu RN

Education

Norwich University

Master's Degree, Nursing Administration · (2014 - 2016)

University of Santo Tomas

Bachelors of Science in Nursing · (1986 - 1990)